sodapdf.com 2016-10-21

# LULU Software SodaPDF Privacy Policy

  * Privacy Policy
  * Terms of Use
  * EULA

## Privacy Policy [ ](https://privacy.truste.com/privacy-seal/validation?rid=94aaae1d-a2fe-421b-9a14-97832c75d05c&lang=en "TRUSTe Privacy Certificati title=")

Last updated: March 2016

**LULU Software** has received **TRUSTe** 's Privacy Seal, signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the **TRUSTe** program. In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. The **TRUSTe** program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The **TRUSTe** program only covers information that is collected through this website: www.sodapdf.com

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact **TRUSTe** at  
<https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:

**LULU Software**  
7075 Robert-Joncas Place, Suite 142  
Saint-Laurent, QC  
H4M 2Z2  
Canada

At LULU Software™, we respect your right to privacy and we are committed to protecting it. This statement discloses the information that we gather and track, how we use the information, and with whom we share this same information as well as the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. This privacy policy covers sodapdf.com

#### Changes to the Policy

If there are changes made to our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change(s) coming into effect.

#### Personal Information

You can visit the Soda PDF website without indicating who you are, and without revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to buy from the Soda PDF website, we ask you to provide basic information such as your first name, last name and email address. This will be used to set up your private account, your invoice, and to send your purchase confirmation. Your personal information will NEVER BE DISCLOSED OR SHARED, SOLD, TRADED OR RENTED TO ANY THIRD PARTIES FOR MARKETING PURPOSES without your explicit consent. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us or to participate in our customization programs, simply indicate your preferences once you sign onto this website. You can opt out of receiving these marketing communications by clicking on the Unsubscribe link in the email.

Transaction information such as credit card details, billing addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses are required to purchase and activate your membership or obtain a software license for our software. We will share that necessary personal information with third parties to process any payment you may make to us. We use service providers such as credit card processing providers, and an email service provider. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.

If you provide us with personal information or credit card information about somebody else, such as a family member, friend or associate, we will assume that you have their permission to do so. If you do provide us with such third party personal information, we will only use it in the manner you have requested. We will store this information for the sole purpose of processing the payment. If you wish to opt out, you may contact us at [info@sodapdf.com ](mailto:info@sodapdf.com)to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### Access

If you would like access to your personal information to correct, update or delete it, please contact us as at:

LULU Software  
7075 Robert-Joncas Place, Suite 142  
Saint-Laurent, QC  
H4M 2Z2  
Canada

All users may also email: [info@lulusoftware.com](mailto:info@lulusoftware.com) and we will respond in a reasonable timeframe.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Minors

If you are under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use this website. If you are 13 years old but not yet 18, or of the age of majority in the jurisdiction where you reside, you may not use this website without the express and enlightened consent of your parent or guardian.

#### Statistics

Note that we will use anonymous information concerning users of this website to make statements and advertisements concerning our community of users. Such statements may contain statistical analysis of the trends or groups within the users of this website, while preserving their, and your, anonymity

#### Use of your personal information

To fulfill your transaction requests, you must allow us to use your personal information to identify you as a client. We may send you service-related emails as a result of this transaction.

#### Information Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

#### Business Transitions

If LULU Software is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

#### Cookies and Other Web Technologies

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by LULU SOFTWARE and our partners, affiliates, analytics, or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

Log Files - As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. Or we may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you with advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. If you do not wish to have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML 5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based on your Web browsing activities use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

#### Security, Intrusion, and Detection

For website security purposes, and to ensure that our website remains available to all visitors, all network traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, cause damage, or conduct criminal activity. To protect the system from unauthorized use and to ensure that the system is functioning properly, individuals accessing our website are subject to monitoring. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable federal law.

#### Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our website includes links to other website whose privacy practices may differ from those of LULU Software™. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

#### Blog

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@lulusoftware.com](mailto:info@lulusoftware.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and widgets, as well as the “Share this” button and all interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page(s) you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Contact Information

LULU Software welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or this website, please visit [www.sodapdf.com](http://www.sodapdf.com/) and choose your preferred method of contact (e-mail or phone)

#### Customer’s Branding

As a paying customer of LULU Software, we reserve the right to use your company-branding and may display Customer’s name, logo, trademarks and service marks within the designated area of the Web pages hosted by LULU Software. LULU Software may prominently display on all Services Pages Company’s name, logo, trademarks, service marks and a phrase substantially similar to “powered by SODA PDF,” or such other phrase as LULU Software may specify from time to time, as well as any names, logos, trademarks, or services marks of third party co-branding clients of Company.

Mac OS user? Discover our free Mac OS Reader.

Learn more __
